Finding Aid for General Clinical Research Center (University of Michigan) publications, 1961-1993
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
General Clinical Research Center (University of Michigan) publications 1961-1993
University of Michigan. General Clinical Research Center.
11 linear feet.
Reprints of medical journal articles describing medical cases and treatment protocols based upon clinical trials in the University of Michigan General Clinical Research Center.
02100 Bimu C500 2
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
Publications are received periodically from the General Clinical Research Center (donor # 7274 ).
The records are open for research.
See the historical sketch in the finding aid for the General Clinical Research Center (University of Michigan) Records.
The General Clinical Research Center Publications (11 linear feet) are comprised of a single series: Unit Publications. The Unit Publications series contains printed material published specifically by the General Clinical Research Center. These publications are defined as being widely distributed and may be published at regular intervals. They are arranged by genre of the publication.
Subjects:
University of Michigan. General Clinical Research Center.
Genre/Form:
Reprints.
- Unit Publications
  The Unit Publications series is made up of forty-eight bound volumes covering the period from 1961 to 1993. Entitled Clinical Research Unit Publications, these volumes are a series of reprints from various medical journals describing medical cases and treatment protocols based upon clinical trials in the University of Michigan General Clinical Research Center. Each volume is arranged alphabetically by the first author listed on the title page of the reprint. There is a table of contents for each volume which has been reproduced for the researcher's convenience and appended to the finding aid. The first volume covers the period from 1961 through 1966. After that there was usually one volume of reprints for each year. Beginning in the year 1986-1987 there are at least three bound volumes for each year.
  - Clinical Research Unit Publications (Box 1)
    - Vols. 1-4, 1961-1971, 5 bound volumes (Box 1)
    - Vols. 5-9, 1972-1978, 5 bound volumes (Box 2)
    - Vols. 10-13, 1979-1982, 5 bound volumes (Box 3)
    - Vols. 17-18, 1985-1987, 4 bound volumes (Box 3)
    - Vol. 19, 1987-1988, 3 bound volumes (Box 6)
    - Vol. 20, 1988-1989, 4 bound volumes (Box 7)
    - Vol. 21, 1989-1990, 3 bound volumes (Box 8)
    - Vol. 22, 90-1991, 4 bound volumes (Box 9)
    - Vol. 231991-1992, 1 bound volume (Box 9)
    - Vol. 23, 1991-1992, 4 bound volumes (Box 10)
    - Vol. 24, 1992-1993, 1 bound volume (Box 10)
    - Vol. 24, 1992-1993, 6 bound volumes (Box 11)